Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Cream Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the Frosted Sugar
Cookie Blizzard. Let me show you how to
make it.
>> This tastes exactly like a Christmas
Frosted Sugar Cookie. Brings me back to
when I was like 12 years old, fat as
just pounding those cookies.
Editor pop up the picture. Yeah,
rough times.
>> Rough times is right. Yeah, I used to be
pretty fat if you guys didn't know. But
for this recipe, we are starting off by
making the frosting. You can either use
a storebought frosting like I showed in
that first clip. Pro tip is to freeze it
so it hardens up a little bit and
doesn't get completely mixed into the
ice cream. Or you can make a protein
frosting by making a whey drip. So if
you just combine 15 g of your favorite
protein powder with a little bit of
water, add slowly, stir it up, you'll
get a kind of protein frosting. So
that's what I did. The base of this
recipe is just a classic vanilla base.
That'll be down in the description. But
while it is running on the light ice
cream cycle, you can grab your mixin.
So, either that frosting or the whey
drip. And then the true key to this
recipe, fuel protein cookie dough bites.
These taste just like those frosted
sugar cookies. I'll have them linked in
my bio. I do have a code with them. One
of the only companies I have a code
with, code FPF. So, after that mixing
cycle is done, you're going to top the
ice cream with those cookie dough bites
and then a few festive Christmas
sprinkles if you have them. Completely
optional.